you know what is that like it seems like
a lot of our age group people are
changing people are growing up have you
noticed that ya know it's it's super I
don't know so much is changing but I
feel like so for so long like
generations prior I've just kind of like
molded sorry to like we're why where we
were at and I feel like amongst our
friend group like we're just trying to
make something different happen a
different outcome like more happiness
and less like structure and like that's
my personal opinion on that we're
growing up but we're seeing that we're
like not growing up happy so we're like
alright we need to be writing up happy
and like in love with life and in love
with what we're doing
yeah yeah yeah totally I feel that too
it's kind of it's it is growing up you
know but it's I don't want you know old
people to be like all finally these kids
are growing up it's it's I think what it
is is great see we chill out my mom's
got us in here just literally just
having a ball with himself he's just
he's having a fight with somebody
yep there he goes I wonder if it's on
the I bet you that this one is recording
it so when we're trying to have a
serious conversation about hilarious all
right we're gonna keep going so it seems
like our you know our age group we grew
up with technology like it was just
growing up just doesn't mean the same
thing as it does for our parents age
like we're like when they turn 18 19 it
was that's when they grew up so to say
or yeah it's like okay let's start doing
what we need to do which is you don't
think it fends get a house 401k all
these things that's a huge
generalization but it seems like argh
our group is finally realizing okay so
that doesn't work for us and we know
that we know that we're not happy doing
what our parents have done there's a lot
more opportunity seems like we can kind
of know more broader subjects and we're
finally able to to figure out what our
growing up I guess is
I suppose like how do we grow out of
this exciting technology like this is
who we are this little subculture yeah
it's like cool that we can differentiate
like different eras like you know like
we're at this point where like I don't
know like for myself personally but like
I'm not you know holding anything
against like what has created the life
that we have now better like more so
trying to just do better for what is yet
to come I thought make sense so it's
cool that way like or really about it no
no it's totally fine it seems like as we
get jamming more we'll just be able to
to just kick it off it's funny I noticed
when I'm talking on the podcast I feel
like I stop myself and I want my long
rambling thoughts a little bit more cuz
I'm like oh yeah people are listening to
be talking I'm probably not talking
about [__] you know but it's funny it's
it's just we're just talking you know
it's funny that we have that little
self-conscious like how I'm not good at
saying what I need to say it's so silly
but yeah luckily I feel like if there's
some listeners that are gonna understand
you know in listen how's word you know
as we're talking and trying to explain
ourselves I feel like these are
different the listeners that'll do so
hopefully hopefully if not [__] you man
if you listening [__] you in your car
I'm gonna turn that up to just like
super loud to some full cool that's
funny I wonder if I overloaded the amp
this is a new loom so you can hear me
now yeah I'm just
it just reflux so what happened is as I
was just going to [__] you into my mic
my new little Amazon headphone port
thing overloaded itself but yes for real
um yeah but so JC I'm really happy to
have you on here and have just like real
conversations that that anybody's
listening can can have value from we've
known each other for quite a while I
mean do you remember how we met at all I
have like I don't remember just through
friends maybe I want to say probably at
a party at your house maybe dire that's
right what is it I started coming
because I'm from you know around this
area and I started like partying super
young so like a team that came into the
coasts of Longview scene right which was
like new culture to me from living out
in the woods - yeah you know 30 people
at least you through that you know just
meeting I think through Zack
specifically cuz I think that's how we
met but I did you know I think a lot of
people yet because I was I was roommates
with Zack it's cool I feel like the
people that we know like a our age group
because because we're four years apart
but like all of us hung out we know so
many people that I feel like we know so
many of the same similar people I was
talking I was with lunch with at lunch
with Shay Lee's mom yesterday and we
were talking about yeah she had her 50th
birthday party she's telling me that you
know people from her childhood came and
friends she was friends with when she
was 16 and 15 you know there's cool
stuff but and I asked her I said did you
like really get many new friends after
high school like it so after high
schools done you know they didn't have
cell phones and Facebook and MySpace and
stuff so it's like like who they know is
who they grew up with and then in I mean
think of like we didn't know each other
in high school I don't think I mean all
the people that we know like all the
people that I met from from living with
Dyer and vice versa it's something new
like we know probably hundreds more
people than our parents did
% yeah it's it's cool but it's also I
think that it's it was such an exciting
thing when it happened you know right
thing off social media now I realized
that like man it's hard to keep up with
that many people yeah you know we're an
interesting time with knowing so many
people it's also I feel like with being
on social media it's a lot easier to
make more and not always the case but
like more of like a synthetic
relationship it's still friendly it's
still cordial it's still nice you said
you care about that person but at the
end of the day it's like you know
there's there's not real raw
conversations because you know 90% of
their life through social media and it's
like such a weird I don't know you know
like our parents didn't have that that
had made these real raw connections that
they had to maneuver through as a child
and like take that with them through
older age and not to say that I haven't
made real rock connections through
social media as well but it's very far
and few in between and so like that's
like you know there's no there's no one
person I think from you know school high
school that I went to school with and
I'm still friends with currently yeah
that's strange to you right yeah do you
think it's um do you think it's I mean
it's gotta be it's because we obviously
are environments like we just don't hang
out the same people but it's because we
change because we grow we adapt I mean I
think that's a huge thing that obviously
our parents know that that they change
from when their childhood but I think
that what our what our generation is
really realizing is that we changed more
than once like we really kind of grow
out of friends sometimes I can for a
couple years even yeah it's it's as much
as we want to hang on to all those
friendships it's it's not about like
letting it go it's about just like not
being so invested in other people's
lives and knowing everything about them
and in like like so like I don't really
know what you've been up to you but
instead of me knowing on social media or
or whatever advice versa
we just like we just took a walk before
this podcast just like caught up and
he's just so great like I find a lot
more value and stuff like that
I know now the time people have a lot of
extra time to just go for a walk with a
friend you know so I'm very blessed with
that but I don't know it I think just
noticing stuff like that is very
beneficial that that's something that
that anybody can benefit from like if
you feel like you're not playing I'm
kind of strong strong connections
anybody listening now if you feel like
you're not feeling strong connections
with your friends and the people around
you like are you hanging out with them
too much are you seeing them too much
are you texting them every waking second
like maybe maybe let them experience
some other [__] and then you goes to
experience some other [__] you guys meet
together next week and talk about it you
know yeah I don't know I think it feels
better that way right like a portion of
that or majority of that is not having
like you were saying earlier and we when
we were on our walk it's like there's
not a lot of present people mm-hmm you
know like we're so drawn to like what's
going on around us you know it's what is
the word that I'm looking for cyber Li
is not even a word yeah did the digital
anything you say in that position is
like sounds like some sort of movie
scenario like whatever you say there's
just stuck with the movies here but we
are so sorry so we're so caught in in
the digital or so we're so caught up in
the technology not present like I try
and you know make it a point that like
and not that I'm high and mighty for
doing this I just tried to make me try
though when I'm with somebody to make
sure that I'm present to make sure that
I'm aware to make sure that I like and
stuffing away you know anything that's
gonna give me a distraction to what the
other person is doing or what we are
communicating about and that's you know
it's not always the case for me but and
I find that you know there's a decent
amount of people who don't take the time
to be present and like what what you're
what's right in front of you like the
person
or the person that's communicating with
you or talking with you or yeah you know
like well isn't it crazy that that we
don't we were talking about how we
didn't realize that we're not doing that
for a long time like being present is so
so anybody so think about any listeners
if that seems overly obvious where that
seems like it doesn't make sense to you
like of course I'm talking to the person
where were your thoughts when you're
talking to somebody are you thinking
about something else are you thinking
about a judgement are you engaged in
listening are you waiting for your turn
to speak are you looking at your phone
these things like it's not like these
are rules and your life suddenly gets
better when you do these things but you
notice how often you weren't doing these
things when you when you make it a point
to try to do them so maybe just next
time you have a conversation next time
you're talking to somebody like are you
standing up straight and looking in the
eyes are you it's your phone in your
hand even are you what's your body
language you know just just being
present in conversations is it's um it's
it's weirdly not easy to do right is
easy to do but it's also like more
monumental than monumental then then you
think it's flavorful weird I like that
that's good yeah but to somebody else
like you never know like how much
somebody just needs like your presence
and like here do you and your effort and
your energy even just for five seconds
or 10 minutes or an hour you know and
that's like moreso
not maybe not more so but like more what
I try to bring aware to myself is
because like you know like I'm sure
you've been in this position or but I
know personally myself I've been in a
position where I've like paid attention
to or wanted somebody to just give me
like a certain fraction of a timeframe
just because I was mentally not in a
spot where like oh that's what you think
I need you just yeah yeah and not
getting that reciprocated which you know
that happens it's where we're at right
but but if you have if you could
recognize it though like if you can if
you can see the times when you weren't
doing it you can you know start to
notice he even have sympathy when other
people aren't doing it like you notice
if other people aren't paying attention
to you you can say like oh okay what's
the thing that I do to like it's okay
maybe you could do something to have
them pay more attention or if it's a
close relationship you can actually have
a conversation with them you know it's
like Shane Lee and I have conversations
all the time you know if if she's on her
phone she's actually able to notice like
oh shoot okay you know what I was kind
of just slacking off on my snapchat for
a few as we were talking and she gets
herself present like I noticed that
stuff now I think it's something we can
all do it's just once you notice it
opens up this penis have you I mean I
just my life has changed drastically
from meditation and yoga and stuff have
you done into meditation now tell me
about your meditation meditation so I
think when you were like jumping off
social media
you were like reaching out for remind
you how long ago was that it's been a
while it's been a long time
yeah it's been I mean it I feel like I
kind of a yeah it's almost about a year
August 10th was like my biggest like
Mike when I have like a moment you know
in my head that something flip but but
but it like led to I think probably over
the next three months I probably to
social media so let's say I don't know
anyway around anyway okay so I think
during that timeframe between like
August and December year they made it a
point to be like hey what are some
things that like helped you with you
know I forgot I did this yeah but you
did you're like what are some things
that you do and like that helped you and
I I started with app on my phone just
because I was like not in a good
headspace at all whatsoever like I was
like totally at my wit's end not happy
and so much so to worry Libby we was
like one of my many therapists I've ever
had which I'm like all for talking about
being open about therapy good for you
yeah but so she it was just like you
know it's at some point like you have to
really try and something that you could
do is like meditate and I was like how
am I gonna sit here and like yeah like
okay I'm just gonna sit here I'm really
anxious and you're telling me just chill
out right it's kind of you know your
brain goes yeah and so I'm gonna sit
here and just like breathe and like
relax and I know I like seemed like a
very low mellow person but my brain is
literally always looping like so high
speed fast pace it's really hard for me
to even like go to sleep at night like
it takes me so long so there's so many
people that are like this so many it's
if you are if you're like this if you
feel crazy all the time that's okay
you're just human we could figure it out
yeah meditation helps for sure I totally
had to utilize that to basically just
dial everything in and it's been a
pretty easy process to get into yeah
just making it kind of routine and just
kind of like guide
nation is where I started and then you
know went from guided meditation to just
kind of like you listen to music just
like mellow music it's just YouTube so
my best friend on that ass absolutely
yeah and it's just it's cool to like not
be in my own head for 10-15 minutes just
as long as the video you know or the the
music or write whatever in its it's
really neat a turning point where I can
not only take those 10 or 15 minutes but
also like learn how to manage and
breathe through everyday life you know
yeah so so I want to I want to try to
describe to people like him I want
people who have tried meditation and
think they failed and I want people who
have never tried meditation but they
think they know something about it cuz
that that I would fall into the second
category out I would be like yeah dude
like I'm not a monk so yeah like like oh
you meditate cool well I have ADHD so if
i sat still I'd go crazy that's living
something I would say so so your your
therapist suggested meditation and so
you just add a little bit like headspace
was that the app user headspace I have
tried that that app I liked it too it's
like yeah I think it was like the one he
has like an Australian voice she's the
most delightful voice this minute I
think it was the thing is this no ya
don't totally know what you're saying
yeah so so when you listen to if you
never listen to a guide a meditation you
know they kind of run you through they
have some basics of what you really do
so they run you through kind of what
your thoughts are doing it's not just
the act of sitting there and something
magical pops out of your butt like yeah
he's it's the act of watching your
thoughts and realizing that you aren't
your thoughts it's mindfulness
meditation is what what it's pretty much
of what it's called in the Western world
so you did a headspace do you remember
like your first time with the meditation
like do you remember how it went and ah
yeah it was like I remember being in
this house and a basement
lived in them shout out to basements
with a very similar gray walls and
family English a degree was no funny
gray Ross and faceless these were
actually wood walls but I painted them
of course but I remember like you know
how when you're sitting like most of
most of the times stereotypically you're
supposed to be like sitting lawyer
meditate of course here I cannot do that
yeah the total I love laying down okay
love just completely relaxing and just
letting like my entire site literally
just laid in bed and I had perfect yeah
I was super that's not doing meditation
wrong like that's not wrong like even if
video says sit on your butt it's like if
you're not sitting on your butt it's
like how [__] this up all right here
I'm brewing his meditation it's you know
you can lean on so you laid down for
your first time yeah and I just played
this guided it's like I think there's
like certain levels only it's been a
long time since I've used every certain
step since I was like level one or step
one you play it and this guy comes up
and I'm just sitting here like oh boy
here we go
weirdo but yeah yeah I know you do
honestly it feels so weird like the
first time you're just like sitting
there because you're solely focused on
like yourself at that point and not like
so much stuff that's surrounding you
you're literally dialed into what is
going on with you and it's like so weird
when for me personally I'm so like oh
we're you know like of other people and
what they're doing in their lives and
what I can do to benefit myself and
their lives you know exactly like that
so it was like really weird for me to
like turn everything in wear it and be
like okay oh [__] this is like alright
here we go
my thoughts are crazy now that I'm
looking at him yeah you know yeah it's
kind of funny when you when you sit down
you know you think there's like
intention like you you have to think how
to not have a thought that's what we
think we have to do like you sit down
and quit doing the thought
yeah that's that's not what you do here
with meditation when you sit down and
and you can download that the app
headspace there's plenty of apps and we
really just try any of them and just so
far the ones that I've tried quite a few
and they've been honestly all great I
think they're great starters it's all
that stuff is at your fingertips like
that YouTube whatever guided meditation
whatever you sit down and you wouldn't
when thoughts come up you don't identify
with them so it's like my leg itches you
can say oh that's a thought about my
legging and then you return to your
breath or whatever the instructor is
telling you that's pretty much the
essence of meditation right that's the
thing it's like for a long time I
remember I don't know if you had this
experience but I was like there's no way
this is all meditation is like it's not
just watching good thoughts like this
doesn't make sense yeah but I don't know
did you have that did you like like were
you shocked to the simplicity of
meditation yeah this is just the concept
of like really having to make it a point
to just like write it out but also like
breathe through what you were thinking
and what you're I don't break this what
you're thinking what you shouldn't be
thinking I guess and even when you like
quote-unquote shouldn't be thinking
something like you stopped to write that
thought out understanding that concept
of like we are human and it's okay to
have these nuts but it's crazy that like
we don't simplify it that much like we
totally expand our thoughts and their
negative thoughts more so than our
positive thoughts oh yeah like we
dissect the crap out of us I know there
are us like it's a I always compare it
this may make sense to you I I try to
crazily explain concepts like this is
Shaylee but I always talk about our maze
like the maze of what we're dealing with
right now like our emotions whatever the
situation is that's happening that we're
so stressed about is just a dead end in
our maze that we're in but the thing
about the maze is you can realize that
you don't even have to be in
Maes so that's what meditation does for
me is instead of trying to sit down and
solve all these problems and like why am
i this way when I'm in this way I can
realize that I can be a layer above this
maze and I even be in it and watch
myself try to solve those thoughts did I
go and I don't have to I don't have to
be in there in that maze to watch my
thoughts and so for me that kind of like
with that an Audi I feel I get it yeah
it expands it I guess I guess suppose it
just helps me identify with not only the
dead ends in the maze but the fact that
I am NOT the maze yeah no that makes it
confusing Spence I just kind of like
instead of going in blindly like you're
you're rising above it and you're just
like yourself to this point where you're
like alright this is this is who I am
I'm not I'm not
yeah I'm not this person that's blind
and lost or negative running to a dead
end or feeling you're like I'm this
person who is just maneuvering through
life and I yeah yeah exactly
I'm glad to get it yeah good so ok
meditation I just want to like to beat
it to a pope so for me so for me it
turned into a daily thing for me but so
you started with the app I'm sure you
probably have some sort of like daily
practice right right now I mean like
what do you I mean it's okay so what
about mindset like do you have like it's
like everlasting mindset that I gave to
you right even though yes yeah so
there's like I started with headspace
and then I kind of grew from there to
like YouTube and other stuff like that
but now it's just I am at a point where
like I can differentiate my thought
process you know that's kind of
beautiful yeah what they gave me and not
that I'm always aware it always yeah of
course human I'm gonna that's the thing
that meditation taught you is that
you're not always like it helps you
sympathize with yourself
but I'm definitely at a point where like
I can say a scenario that happens it's
just like negative instead of like
choosing to go down a negative path or a
negative thought process I'm just like
yeah whatever any hole any like that's a
possibility
it's a dead-end in the maze that I could
take but like I'm not even go into that
maze yeah yeah which I think that that's
super cool
I like haven't really brought awareness
of that even so thank you for pointing
that out
but that's that's yeah that's definitely
what has what I've like grown into
through meditating even just the last
you know I wouldn't two years I want to
say right yeah do you like now that so
like let's just generalize like a
meditative mindset let's just call that
like just you know whether the the act
of looking at the fact that your
emotions and your actions couldn't be
biased
you know the are that we're not always
perfect but that's okay you know just
just observing our thoughts rather than
being our thoughts this mindset like it
happened for you like two years ago or
so or not to use more with it slowly
started the process mm-hmm like two
years ago so it wasn't like an immediate
like it was some work it's it's a lot of
work yeah so I think that's what people
need to hear right is that like in that
there's part of that parts of that where
you almost dread you're like well great
like cool I I don't have two years until
I can get better you know like [__] but
that's how life goes like but it's if
you just take one step towards like you
just sat down and you're like I don't
automatically download you just take the
things in your life that and just face
at them maybe it's gonna take a couple
years and we're always working out so
that's it's so funny that you say that
that was I think one of the biggest when
I literally had like my one of my
therapists look at me be like it takes
work to be happy mm-hmm just like I
think about that every day that was like
does he have years ago and I'm like
every time some he's like
so sad and I'm like me and I really care
for you and I'm really sorry like I make
it a point to be like it does take a lot
of work to be ready so if you genuinely
like want to put in the work and the
effort you like it's not gonna you're
not gonna wake up one morning and be
like man I'm so happy I like that yeah
it's it's so funny because it's like no
[__]
right of course we know that but then
sometimes you can be in a moment where
you're susceptible and you're ready to
hear it's like you you have that moment
your therapist like what you think you
heard it and you're like okay and do you
think at that moment he was probably
like hard-hitting right you hear this
thing in exams right yeah you know I
think and so like these podcasts are
stuff like that - like which is it's
gonna open up this can of whoop-ass
which is just I'm super pumped about but
I think by having more upfront
conversations like this and talking
about like our faults you know as
friends I think I hope that it can open
up conversations between friends not
just on podcast but like why not have
situations where our homies are our
counselors and saying I came in your
you've not been doing what you want to
do and I know you better than that you
know but we can't have those
conversations because my friends just
like they think they're being attacked
personally and whatever but there's a
lot of people who love you and not that
everybody's opinion is is always valid
like sometimes people just don't know
what you're going through but I don't
know I think it we could you see could
you see like our world and you know
let's say next five years like where we
can just call each other out like this
like not like this but yeah just say if
you had a podcast you ain't call each
other no but yeah I do I kind of I
already see it I'm already like amongst
you know a decent amount of paper and it
could just be that I like love being
around people who like to call me on my
[__] right but you know and vice versa
is sick not afraid to sit down to be
like hey this is what's up but I do
totally see it evolving into that kind
of like friendship level where we can
just like sit down mainly because like
there's a lot of broken people
a lot of broken people who don't know
what to do or which way to go and then
there's like a decent amount of people
who have gone through like a situation
or scenario or I don't I don't really
know like what to call it where you just
kind of I I think evolving quick
involvement I mean waking up is what the
internet calls it but like I feel like I
miss BAM like I feel like the first
comment on my YouTube is gonna be woke
AF this is WellCare or something I'm not
I know I like to say a shift like you
you just shift into like this this
person who is beneficial to those
surrounding you and yourself actually
but and so I you know I feel like as
being one of those persons I mean not to
me like you are what else person you are
you're on the junker left podcast you
are it's pretty much hey by the way if
you're on the junk love podcasts um
I plan on going places so yeah you're
going to have a responsibility whether
you're here whether you want to be here
not you I feel like I want to like just
make a bunch of pressure on people be
like hey this is really important but
it's just me like smoking weed or
something like I'm just doing nothing
you know I'm playing with play-doh on my
podcast me this is so important
skateboard you still have it oh yes you
do perfect that's just what you doing
here I'm devastated I don't worth that
pause the podcast so I technically
there's even people who want to watch
tactics you know people want to watch
people skateboard there's plenty there's
little kids who are famous for tech
decking you have their entire College
paid for probably where we live in yeah
it's actually pretty cool no I know
props to the parents who made it a point
to make their children's college and
success through YouTube
well he you don't be weird imagine
imagine the [__] that you're into when
you were
being how you make a million dollars
like what were you into when you were
seven or eight years old or some [__] I
think I think I baked a lot like Easy
Bake Ovens it's no think like you baked
yeah real baking yeah see that would
have been actually fruit Allah that's
like the worst example of I'm like what
if you did Polly Pockets forever
I don't really know still bake yeah I
mean for my own pleasure I mean that's
still I mean there dude food tastes
better when it's you know you put love
and time into it and and you spend time
making it yeah it's mostly out of a box
in your butt right it still tastes good
so it's yeah so you just eat it right
off the box huh just open it up an eater
a box she used to be a baker as she grew
up and now she just puts her hand into
the box of brownie mix and eats it dry
mouth think about it yes but yeah no I
can not imagine being seven years old
and creating a success off of my
interest how cool would that be
I mean it'd be cool but being a lot of
pressure like think about like you okay
I'm seven I just did this thing alright
I'm done with that like now I'm fourteen
I really got a what's my next stage in
life like these little kids have like
they've just done the thing like like as
a kid
all you want is a quest you know like
you just like if you just give me a
quest I will follow this quest yeah
it'll be my destiny like I want to
believe in something and like we all
have you know we're like I want to be a
firefighter or astronaut or whatever
they have you write down and it's cool
it's like imagine actually getting those
kids who get that like they're like I
want to be I want to review Hot Wheels
on YouTube I don't know if it's good or
bad to give kids exactly what they want
I think in that situation it depends on
the person I guess I mean the child
could be great though but think about I
mean think about again this person has
to now later on in life they have to be
20 years old they have to be a 21 year
old they have to
like I don't know I always think about
Minecraft oh yeah or like they've
already done it like they've already
like a live or they've already decided
who they were like I went through so
many stages growing up like I was you
know whatever I would do or try to be to
battle the personal issues that I was
going on you know like I guess that
would be pretty depressing successful
when I fourteen years ago when I was
seven so what the [__] do I do with my
life now would it solidify whoever the
hell you think you are when you're seven
like I'm Lego master I may be when
you're 25 you're like I'm still Lego
master what do you mean mom don't you
remember
and she's like fold your clothes
what are you moving out what are you I'm
a star mom that would be almost a crisis
maybe not though yeah I think not always
getting what you want is such a blessing
learning experiences you don't get to
learn much if you always get what you
want
ya know I definitely feel like going
going through all of the hardest in most
light like through my lifetime
like all of those were definitely
experiences like I wouldn't have evolved
or shifted into this person that I am
today without having like a trip trial
and error and like you know being
frickin negative thirty five dollars in
my account for stupid overdrive yeah
been there plenty of times sometimes
they just keep coming out and you're
like I am negative $200 because four
things came out yeah we know how it goes
it's weird that like so even casual
conversations about being broke can only
be it seems like even that in our normal
conversation it's always like a joke you
think a joke out of like oh I'm poor or
whatever I'm broke
but it's dude if you're going through
financial [__] like just so you know
everybody has gone through financial
[__] like yeah the people who have it
all together like aren't trying to walk
around saying that they have it all
together it's like I don't know I I
think but my friend me and my friend
Scott we're talking about we grew up
together and we kind of we're talking
the mindset behind finances you know
like we're both like me and we both kind
of always sucked in money like it's just
been this thing you know but I think
realizing that the person to your left
and the person to your right like
sometimes they have money issues too
yeah like like it's okay to talk about
them like you don't have to like demean
yourself you don't feel bad whatever
it's I think that that's a part of life
and that's a part of growing because I
can't without having those like failures
that financially especially being a
young adult like life Sarge shit's
expensive anymore and so like with
having those without having those
struggles like I don't think that I
would have the drive to like do more for
myself financially or do you know what I
mean yeah it was like totally normal
like I being negative in my bank account
as a 20 year old or 21 year you know
back whatever like that's fine like but
did you you isn't it funny how like it
often will me anyway I feel like such a
[__] failure sometimes when I was
broke I think if I didn't have any money
I would just be like gosh like dude like
I didn't get my [__] together like I'd
always feel like I don't have my [__] to
get like that's what that means so much
bunch of money in my account means I
don't have my [__] together
ya know I definitely was low you feel
pretty low about yourself you feel like
okay well I mean this is something that
I can acquire what am i doing that like
is do you know making this not easy for
me but it it's not it's not easy that's
the thing it's like you feeling that low
just like that's my mean like that that
gives me the drive to just like yeah get
my [__] together correctly I mean it's I
don't know well so that's the thing is
it is that's the thing it's like it's
okay like but you got to look at look at
these things as like yeah it's okay like
I don't have to hate myself but like I
don't have money but I want money okay
what can I do differently like not not
what can what has the world done wrong
to me that's given me not the
opportunities that I want for money
yeah it's it's what can I do different
like when you when
you have those because I think of you
know like rich kids or kids who like
somehow I have money you know I'm like
come into them it's something like if
that's the case for you that's awesome
yeah if if you never learned what it is
to not have it and in what it is - I
guess you learn the hard way yeah it's
something that like the learning
experience people don't actually always
get know which is you know more about
you if you can go through life that way
and come out of you know decent human
being and know for real still like the
you know but yeah at the end of the day
it's like when you really have to grind
for it that's almost like when you reach
that level of success like when you have
to grind for it and not not saying I'm
there like right but reaching that level
or that point of success after you've
grinded for it for so long after being
so depressed because you're negative and
your bank account is like such a
humbling feeling it's like you're
depressed if you're if you are like
broke right now and you're depressed
like just know like let that feel you
and Drive you for that humbling
experience you know when you reach your
goal or destination sex financial you
wait yeah exactly our pains like our art
pains and our issues like where we okay
I'm broke like this is an issue that I
need to solve that's that's something to
solve and when you when you see that as
something you could solve then that's
how your life gets better like those are
it's like gonna cop my life couldn't get
better I don't know how to make my life
better okay we'll take a look here she
is and start solving them individually
you know say like money is a big issue
for me what's going on my money
situation when you look at it and you
start just trying to solve it that's one
step closer to getting better this is
one little thing it's yeah I feel like
even putting out like I think I just I'm
like I post a lot like you you've logged
on your junkyard love okay so like I
write like I'll post a picture and I
might started writing like really long
intricate like
just because I I personally am really
uncomfortable and friend seeing you know
seeing yourself no I am too I'm working
on that planet to hear myself that's
right yeah I do I got it but I just I
blog everything so I posted the other
day about like after hitting a huge
milestone in my life I like very shortly
became very sad afterwards and due to
not having goals and ambitions because
goals are legitimately back this is a
totally no I would love to cover this
area but I like sat down with my
boyfriend and just like had a
conversation and was talking and I was
like and he felt very similar which he's
not like a very sad person
and so we just like sat down and had
this conversation of like okay what are
we doing what do we need to change
what's happening and he's like I think
that we just was brave yeah yeah we were
just like so excited to hit this huge
milestone for us that we didn't plan
anything after and so we just kind of
like hit this wall had this breakthrough
and there was like nothing to follow
that nothing no goals to hit no nothing
exciting I mean it was exciting but like
he works realistically like so we must
sat down and like made it a point to
like continue making like goals no
matter what it is big or small like make
a list of you know like what do we need
to do next and that's like really been
like a turning point for me just because
you know I worked so hard and I'm being
happy all the time and let that comes
with having goals and having visions and
like we have something to work for you
have something to be happy about yeah
cuz cuz how else do you gauge your
happiness like how do you host you know
how you're doing yeah like hey like how
you doing man like we never know how to
answer that anyway maybe it's because we
really don't know like how you doing
working toward your goals I don't know
what my goals are so I don't know what
I'm working towards yeah we're not we're
not living to just live as long as we
can we should all be living towards our
own virtues our own goals our no value
yeah so so when you if you're cool
talking about it when you and Jace like
how did this conversation go like I
imagine there's probably plenty of
people who you know there's a lot of
relationships where we're a lot of
people it's hard to get on the same page
you know we're so layers deep in our our
arguments or our pit enos that we don't
really realize that we're doing
sometimes when these conversations start
to come up they get and it seems like a
little too quick without with our
emotions I'm I know I've been there
Shaylee zou it's been there you know in
certain situations how did this
conversation go so it's like hey like
I'm just I don't know what it is I'm not
feeling super super great like what can
we be doing differently or I think it's
started with I'm just a very like
sensitive human being I'm very emotional
and I'm very wait you girl yes and like
that it's a very weird position to be in
a lot of the times and so I'm very
expressive and I'm very like I will
write out my emotions and I will be so
raw and so real tune extent like I'm not
so extreme where you know hurts my
everyday life yeah but you are yourself
and yourself as an emotional person yeah
yeah and that's totally okay and I'm
super you come in terms of that that
like that's just who I am and that's
like know people shout out yeah yeah of
course actually but so going through
that I made it a like I'm just very
expressive so I'm very low-energy
you know just very symptomatic of just
being and just a little depressive funk
which still happens as happy as I am
that still is a battle I have to fight
through every so often and I'm okay with
that too you ever done yes no no I think
it was probably like a few days of just
like going through the motions of like
getting up going to work coming home
like I like when I stopped making dinner
as I cook I like I cook often you love
cooking yeah well you like baking stuff
yeah
like the end of cooking yeah yeah but so
and I just left a really home-cooked
meal so no something you know I grew up
with my dad so that's something that I
just learned from him so because
breeding you know it's not just the food
yeah and so when I stopped making cooked
meals Jace is like he's like woman who
make me yeah so he knew something is
wrong like you know it's gone gone sorry
thank you like made it a point and I'm
just like sitting on the couch or
watching Netflix I'm like not talking
because they just kind of shut down like
is go within myself and dig deep and you
know figure out what I need to do and so
he just like made it a point to say like
hey pin what's up yeah wrong no no I'm
just really sad I've just been sad for a
few days I'm just trying to like power
through it you know because I think and
he's like why are you sad and that was
just like I don't I don't know like I'm
just you know like I haven't figured it
out yet cuz you don't know where it's
coming from I think that's that sentence
right there I just want to pause in that
because I think for me a lot of like me
getting to a point where I can explain
myself to Shaylee a little better you
know because like when I was like very
depressed and very like not having great
thoughts there was little years where
she didn't know like I would she did not
know that I was good what I was going
through like any anxiety tax like and in
those situations she would want to
understand and I would just shut down
and so the Chi she would do what Jay
said is like like what's going on like
what's wrong or something and I would
just shut down so I wish I just wanna
point out like it's great that you're
like you know honestly I don't know I
don't know and that's okay like we don't
always know it's like man so I'm just
[__] it off right but as we're
probably about to get to you probably
started talking and like once you guys
get kind of Tennison
you know like the ideas back to each
other like okay so what's going on like
it's not this like I don't know it just
seems like whatever once you get talking
with
who cares about you and you care about
it kind of falls out so you don't always
have to already know what's going on but
if you feel like you're in a weird funk
like just maybe sit if a damn dinner
table or sitting on couch and whatever
just be us with your significant other
so yeah so so you brought it up to Jace
or Jace brought it up to you and you
were very susceptible to it what where
to go from here I'm like yeah I totally
get the shutting down part and that's
like if you need to go through that
that's totally okay to go through that
and just know a bit like it took me a
long time to even get to the point where
like I can look at somebody and be like
you know here's here's the there's a tee
here's what's going on right and so I
yeah I just made it a point and it
wasn't it wasn't like this smooth this
conversation right off the bat it's kind
of weird like I feel like sometimes when
you're with somebody who's a little bit
more structured in the in the best way
Jace is like the most growth mindset
awesome dude I know yeah so he I'm gonna
have him on here just say deal it so it
means there's no he'll be uneasy for me
I'm very like go through the motions
allow myself to be depressed for two
weeks and nothing denarian Jace is like
what do I need to do right here right
now like to fix this and blah blah so in
like a very like
contradicting conversation but the
outcome was good because like it kind of
brought awareness that like I was like
hey I'm I'm sad and he's like well what
do you need to do to fix it I'm just
like I don't even know why I'm sad but
then yeah we should do I come family
when he figured out me know but yeah if
you know if any or google searches have
any answer it's just if you could send
me that link no he's literally like the
like greatest minds out all the time so
he's a powerful dude
yeah but so yeah we like took me a
couple of days and then like for him to
have a day off and then I think I came
home from work because we have like one
day off throughout the week in one day
that were like
you know so I worked a full day and he
was at home he's like ya know I just
like really feel like once we moved in
here things just kind of like plateaued
and so he took that day and he was like
yeah I just really had to dig deep and
that's where he like sat down and like
he's made you know his list of goals and
stuff and then we like communicated and
he was just like yeah I think that we
really need to like work toward
something else and you know build this
life and continue building and you know
like I feel like we just got so excited
on this high of like buying or starting
a new chapter in our lives that we kind
of forget that our lives continuously
keep going even out of that chapter and
like yeah you started chapter one and
then you just like oh [__] we got to
write a book I think that that's the
beauty then that's the thing that's
that's what life will always teach you
you know if you really think back think
about the things that you have now sorry
but the things that you have now and you
know there is a point where you you
dreamt of having them like they're all
you wanted you know okay like I even
like look like like this [__]
microphone you know like when I bought
it I probably obsessed over it for like
the four hours I think I probably looked
at all the different options or whatever
it might have been you got to take time
to like enjoy the things you're doing
but then like but then say okay what's
our next thing we're doing what's our
because your life is those in-between
your life isn't that moment where you
finally have the trophy in your hand
it's it's getting to the trophy yes it's
it's how do I get another trophy and
it's yeah life is life is a book that
like I feel like as humans we forget
that and it's so basic like meditating
you know it's not always grasp like when
you reach like your destination I guess
like the end goal the end game it's like
not as fulfilling as you expected thank
you like it is and then a visit it's
like all right on to the next like we're
such a moving species yeah
and that we forget that like the
movement is like what Creed's
who we are right it's about the movement
I am I listen to a lot of album Lots you
know he said philosopher I feel like he
has this he has this thing he talks
about and it was it was one of my ha
moments one of my favorite things to do
is listened I can put him on like I'm
dizzy YouTube and I put him in my
headphones I walk in the backyard and
just let the revelations come he had
this thing he's talking about dancing
like what is it dance little life is
like advance we to be the best answer
it's not about getting from here to
there the fastest it's not about a
destination it's to be the best singer
to be the best guitar player it's not
about playing the most notes the fastest
it's it's that in-between you know what
you don't dance if you asked an answer
why they dance they don't say so I can
get from here to there in the most
efficient way it's it's the in-between
like that's that's what life is you know
and he I remember I had this moment he
said that and I've been like working
through much stuff and it was so gravel
Ettore I'm like that seems so simple and
it seems I can make sense but it can be
really a revelatory statement something
great yeah that's Alan Watts it's like
my favorite philosopher if anybody wants
to dive into if you just ever want to
let your mind go just Alan Watts on
YouTube just explore him yeah but yeah
that in between I think so goal-setting
it kind of keeps that in-between alive
you know like making sure that like so
you guys probably have some sort of and
it'll get better over the years I'm sure
but you guys probably have some sort of
like I hate next Sunday let's sit down
look at our goals or you guys have
anything like that leave it's something
I'm working okay we haven't quite got
there but we're we're kind of we would
talk about that like it's something
we're gonna be doing soon like we need
to slow down a little bit to be able to
do that or but we're both like in this
weird so I would love that I would love
to just sit down and
have this like recap of stuff but you
know when you're like little bit you
know like I'm sure when Shelly comes
home like from work and you're like hey
let's sound and have a conversation she
says oh yeah poor thing she's talking
about c-diff and I'm talking about like
existential crisis is my yeah like she
just she just wants to just be like babe
stop talking about so much intent she
right now ya know I mean we definitely
will find time for it I mean yeah III
know I well I'm sure you guys will too
but it's something that is important we
got to make time we can and it's not
always like hey we don't have the time
to talk about it it's like in passing
like next time you and Jace go to dinner
you guys can chitchat about it casually
or whatever you know like fine times in
your relationship - not when we need to
do this thing this way if there's
something that maybe needs to talk about
if you guys maybe aren't if you guys
aren't both pursuing a goal right now in
your relationship if you're listening
for this you don't have to be that how
do we fix this right now it's not that
it's it's hey like you you ever thought
about make it a goal you ever thought
about writing down our goals babe like
that right there is working that's
getting better that's self-love that
question right there it's just a little
nudge you have more questions like that
they add up and then finally if you have
time you know when we have time and a
lot of busy - we can sit down hey let's
write up more of our goals and let's
write out goals in the first place or
feel like that's like a very healthy
standing point to like either be in or
have a goal to be in that situation with
your significant other like to move
forward and grow not only within
yourself but with it somebody you know
signs I and I feel like that's very
important that's that's a pretty big
deal like if you think about it like
saying like okay this person doesn't
know [__] about their life like we don't
know why we're here we don't know where
we come from we're gonna world go when
we die
but same for me and I'm gonna take the
responsibility of them and they're gonna
take responsibility and we're gonna try
to figure out what we both equally think
is best for our lives yeah that's crazy
man like that's that's something we
should take a little more serious I
think yeah
seriously but also like paying attention
to your self yeah going through that cuz
like yeah you always know you know feel
it yeah you always you always feel like
which direction you're going or what you
need to be doing or you know but we as
humans like to just you know make up
scenarios I know you know or what is it
somebody told me the other day they were
talking about red flags or like Oh red
flags I know what I need to be doing but
I'm just like making making up excuses
you know you make excuses to like not
follow your gut not do what you know you
have to do that yeah yeah we're really
really good at that but it's also
learning experience too when you do do
that so yeah I think I say justifying
your [__] I think we really like
justifying your [__] we are doing a
fraud I was saying my burp oh not
knowing or you don't know what you don't
know the
I mean lost it it floated away that
happens I feel like that happens when
you try and focus on it too like solely
away like I know we we had I think it
was me and you see to me McHale moms or
me and Jessica we're out here and you
know like just getting better at
conversating over time like just the
more you do it but it's funny you
realize you kind of get going and you
know nobody's ever let me like talk for
this long
thank you it's funny podcast I've
noticed I'm like oh wow like because you
know it's it's a respectful like we're
both a year to say we want to say but
like me I'm like oh yeah you know no
don't just wait like let let her talk
you know it's we got it we got to do
that like it's it's really it's
something that of course I want to just
burst out what I'm saying but you got to
work on in conversations and you notice
that like sometimes people don't
actually let you talk for this long and
you get to a point like I don't know
what to say anymore or I forgot what I
was talking about I was just so excited
that you were letting me talk and it's
really funny but you got to be be
forgiving with yourself I noticed that I
used to do this and I would trail off
and I lose my thought so to say and I
would I would call myself an idiot on
and say that gotta be like [__] you
gonna can't [__] even keep my thoughts
straight or whatever I get stressful
though sometime right yeah but but it's
like like you do it
everybody have had on this broadcast
does it I do it every person I've ever
talked to them in whole life yeah it's
you remember you're human you know it's
you notice when you're you're kind of
giving yourself little beating yourself
up a little bit about that like it's
like losing your train of thought makes
it's like a lot of anxiety you're like
mmm when you're like just talking
sometimes I find myself talking through
like not really paying attention but
like knowing what I'm saying just
literally letting whatever I'm saying go
right and then I like catch myself at
the end like where was I going with that
and I'm like yeah I know you're like
wait was that down like a rabbit hole
where I wasn't actually making sense
yeah it's so funny you looking at you
know an introspective of just the way
that you talk the way that you you know
and we were talking about when you
record yourself you
differently like you you almost make it
okay to talk crap to yourself like Oh
like pull your shirt down because you
look fat or you you're recording
yourself when you say something wrong in
the class [__] and you delete it or like
you like if someone else was speaking
and they messed up over the words you
would be like you know delete know as
they're talking yeah you gotta be you
gotta be more forgiving on yourself it's
something we all gotta work on I think
that for me I would say I know a lot I
would say I know I know I got to work on
that or I know I'm been at that or um
I'm getting better at it whatever and
then I wouldn't actually look at it and
change it so if you're someone who just
says I know yeah that's cool so you're
like meditating for 30 days and then
sober yeah so I was thinking so but so
okay so do you watch the Joe Rogan
podcast at all yeah
Jase more so than myself of course dude
I love Joe otherwise I can't even deny
it like it's just the most wonderful
community it's [__] hilarious like
there's different means make memes
making fun of people who listen to Joe
Rogan every day and they're just so
funny like sure yeah my going so real I
am one of those little buggers
have you tried to empty you know like
it's so so I was inspired by that you
know they have their whole friend group
that that does that and I was I was
looking at that and I really had a
moment of you know realistically you
know call it cocky or strange to point
out that you want but like a lot of
people I've stayed in the same hometown
like I have actual I would say small
town fame from being a DJ in in a small
town like it's a weird thing to point
out on your own but like it's something
that you have so I have people who look
up to me have people who who do follow
what my friend group does and like it's
something that I have like taking a step
and I'm like okay like cool maybe it's
just me being excited about it but it is
kind of like Joe and his friends cool
let's say that and when it like
everybody really tried and like all
these people who have never worked out a
day in their lives
people who probably have never meditated
a day in their lives because they enjoy
Joe Rogan and his friends whenever they
tried this thing they didn't serve
October I think hundreds and thousands
of people like lost weight and did all
these things tried things for 30 days
whatever so like I don't know I just see
see my role as potentially could maybe
be that in this in in in our area and
like not that I'm trying to be that but
I'm saying if people are looking up to
me if there's something that I want to
do on my own anyway might as well just
do a little extra work be public about
it my friends are gonna do it anyway
like my close friends you know might as
well get everybody else on board so yeah
I think it'd be fun cool yeah what what
else what else do you think we should do
let's so what would you do what would be
something that you would want to do for
30 days like draw for 20 minutes a day
or whatever like just think of anything
read yeah I guess I'm like a super I
love just like reading mm-hmm
self-help books oh yeah I I was just a
better term for it but self-help yeah I
feel like a dork when you go to the
library and there's yeah I shouldn't you
shouldn't feel like a dork though but I
just a lot of monumental moments in my
life I've been like literally reading a
self-help book that's probably super
cheesy but I don't care because I yeah
so you know like I would not be here
today without reading all these books so
for 30 days of reading whatever solid
yeah see you wanna yes that would be
cool you know that that what would be a
cool way to portray that yeah like so so
so what do you think like 30 minutes a
day or like a li sit down or or like cuz
I think you know trying to let me read
this many books in 30 days okay making
it a daily habit of just reading like a
couple pages or mmm make sure you get
some reading done a day yeah yeah I
think that's enough has to be a time
frame
if you sometimes if I like set a certain
timeframe like I'm at the gym and I'm on
the bike and it's like 20 minutes I'm
like I don't really want to do this for
20 minutes like you know I'm gonna go do
a lick or go anyway so like when I see
that and I don't finish something 20
minutes I'm like damn I didn't even do
that 20 minutes but well it builds
habits with yourself it kind of like
trains your brain in the wrong ways I
feel like like if you don't if you
continuously not commit to things that
you really want to do I think it kind of
trains your brain to like pick no that's
okay if you don't do that like oh you
you you want to eat healthy for 30 days
we're at day 17 it's okay it's okay
you're fine you don't have to you don't
have to eat healthy anymore you said
you're gonna go for 30 days I feel like
it like adds up like after enough for
those do just because I used to do that
too like I would I would go it's 20
minutes was my thing - I love 20 minutes
on the stair steppers what I would do
and I would get like oh today is a 10
minutes day huh okay I'm tired it's like
no setup to what you want to do sorry I
keep getting nasally you just talked
about allergies earlier huh I know I
know I'm like fighting my my mom's cat
and I'm like I don't know I'm pushing my
allergies with my mom's cat I'm
convinced the diet has everything to do
with no I seriously oh geez 100% yeah
100% believe yeah everything that you
put into your body oh listen that they
can fake [__] so you can't pronounce
yeah it's yeah no totally even just
switching from being like no fast food
to like home-cooked meals right is a
significant difference I can only
imagine I like more power to you effort
living that lifestyle because I struggle
oh I haven't been lately don't worry you
know this struggle it's it's it's hard I
mean I still make a million little
decisions better today than I did a year
ago you know like I I used to like drink
energy drinks and and go to the gas
station and eat crappy food and fast
food stuff all the time yeah it's it
happens
right yeah but making like little
sacrifices here and there and not you
know having cooked home-cooked meals
when you can it's I feel like it helped
my my cognitive function like my brain
and eating fast food and stuff you think
that just hurts your stomach but all
that shit's connected you know
oh yeah that's all stomach is a pit of
your entire being but in your stomach it
comes out all of your pores and
everything like that it affects a lot of
you like it's so did you did you ever go
through thing where you eaten like a lot
of fast food have you ever gone through
that I just I have I've gone through
literally like years and frankly I hate
fast food pretty much every day I don't
know about every day probably when I was
like 19 and I was just basically an
alcoholic because that's you to at 19
right yeah for like our whole culture is
like well yeah we're just of course
we're drunk we're ages 17 through 22
Thanks
yeah so you know you'd get those dollar
49 Burger King nuggets for oh yeah you
know with rice sauce that was like
talked about all the time yeah but it's
but it's easy right it's it's easy which
is is what it's there for like it's if
you know when you're on a rush like fast
food is definitely faster is there for
what it's like hey I gotta do all these
things I'm in a rush or maybe like a
treat or something but it's it really
does benefit when you just try to not be
eating that crap all the time yeah I'm
trying to cook at home oh for sure or
more so just like finding a healthier
alternative but like that has been my
biggest because sometimes I'm too busy
and I'm like don't have time to just
like go home like I'm home very late at
night and making sure that like I'm
eating something that's like not a
burger through you know and easy for you
to yeah yeah but when you go through the
periods I'm sure you've recognized this
when you go through periods of time
frames where you eat healthy and then
you like switch back to eating unhealthy
you're paying for three years your body
hates you
seriously your body what the [__] are
you putting in me right now I thought we
were done with that yeah I built up
immunities to those things and made you
just permanently bloat it I thought it's
what you wanted it's crazy yeah and it's
like your body is like rejecting like no
I told you no we already went through
this
yeah it's that weird you you can eat
McDonald's every day and you almost get
used to it at some point and then you
like you eat an apple or something
healthy everybody just has the shits or
something and then vice versa you eat
healthy and you just have one yeah I
don't know it's it's you know I feel
like everybody kind of notices that but
it's another one of those things that
worth like and I know it's a it sucks
yeah I'm working on getting getting
better at food you know but I think just
just keep trying like literally just
keep you never you never fail this stuff
like we're we are so as a society we're
so addicted to sugar so addicted to food
in like it's okay like it's it's okay
like it sucks don't be mad at yourself
if you realize this like if what I've
read this first time you realize in the
year severely addicted to sugar unless
you are knowingly eating paleo and
you're listening to this then you're
eating whole thirty you're [__]
addicted to sugar so addicted but it's
just start making little little things
you know like if you drink 17 diet cokes
at a drink 16 today drink 16 and a half
like anything then learn a little bit
make little sacrifices cook when you can
find some value in cooking like I mean
it seems like you and Jace have I'm sure
there's even togetherness from you like
cooking food you know like it just that
creates even stronger boundaries in your
relationship just cooking being at home
in the kitchen you know yeah there's a
lot of value in doing these things with
intent you know yeah especially when
your life's wild man certainly is as
we're trying to slowly figure it out I
know at least we're trying yeah trying
trying really means dude like
trying doesn't mean that you ever really
fail life or less trying means that you
every day all these little things all
these different parts your life if
you're not feeling the way you want to
be feeling mentally you just got to be
trying you gotta be under it but but to
try you have to understand that you
you're not a victim to it anymore you
got it you can help the things that
you're going through yes yeah for a
while here I want to do a time check for
you okay
jaesi think you were coming to this I
appreciate you you've been on the junket
I love podcast yeah super fun super
great conversation yeah well and I I
also plan on like I don't have any rules
I don't have a [__] director like I
can do whatever I want this is me
talking to my cool friends so we can
schedule another one too if you have
more stuff if there's in the next few
months if there's something weighing on
you if you meet somebody that you're
like man this person would be cool like
just come on with him
you can come on with Jace - that'd be
fun - I want definite one day yeah I
want to do a powwow with just me and
Jace but I think it'd be fun to have you
get on there too you know because people
I mean people I know a lot of cool
people and I feel like it's kind of like
it's like an honor of mine to showcase
cool people to whoever's willing to
listen
appreciate it
yeah I appreciate you coming well thank
you so much all right guys have a good
rest your day
you